Finding aid to the Lara Frater research files on fat acceptance SSC.MS.00798
Sophia Smith Collection
Lara Frater research files on fat acceptance
1987-2017
Sophia Smith Collection
Frater, Lara
SSC.MS.00798
.5 linear feet (1 letter document box)
Lara Frater is an author and activist for fat acceptance. This collection includes books, magazines, pamphlets, conference information, and memorabilia related to fat acceptance.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Collected and gived by Lara Frater
Biographical / Historical
Lara Frater is an author and activist for fat acceptance. Her 2005 book, "Fat Chicks Rule! How to Survive a Thin Centric World," was billed as advice on navigating the world as a plus-sized woman. She has since published other essays, poetry, and short stories, as well as several science fiction novels. She currently lives in New York City with her husband, Jonathan Frater.
Books; Fat Studies -- United States -- History -- Sources; Frater, Lara; Frater, Lara
- "Fat is Contagious" conference packet, 2008 February 23; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 1)
- Magazines (New York Times, Grace, Mode), 2003, 2010; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 1)
- News clippings, 1997, 2005; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 1)
- Papers, correspondence, and articles, 1992-2008; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 1)
- Tales of the Closet graphic books (No. 2, 3, 7), 1987, 1988, 1992; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 1)
- Pins, keychains, magnets, approximately 1995-2006; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 1)
- Pamphlets, business cards, note pad, approximately 2006-2017; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 1)
- Lara Frater's Fat!So? day planner, 2012; 1 items (1 item) (Box 1)
- The Fat Studies Reader, edited by Esther Rothblum and Sondra Solovay, 2009; 1 items (1 item) (Box 1)
- Taking Up Space: How Eating Well and Exercising Regularly Changed My Life by Pattie Thomas, Ph. D., 2005; 1 items (1 item) (Box 1)
- The Earth, My Butt, and Other Big Round Things by Carolyn Mackler, 2003; 1 items (1 item) (Box 1)
- Skinny Women Are Evil: Notes of a Big Girl in a Small-Minded World by Mo'nique and Sherri A. McGee, 2003; 1 items (1 item) (Box 1)